[
    {
        &dia_continue#
        Original English: "Continue"
        Translation: "継続"
    },
    {
        &dia_0#
        Original English: "Blacksmith"
        Translation: "鍛冶屋"
    },
    {
        &dia_1#
        Original English: "Ah, you found me."
        Translation: "ああ、見つけてくれたか。"
    },
    {
        &dia_2#
        Original English: "There is an outpost nearby, I could use your help."
        Translation: "近くに前哨地がある。手を貸してくれないか。"
    },
    {
        &dia_3#
        Original English: "Very well, I'll meet you there."
        Translation: "分かった、そこで会おう。"
    },
    {
        &dia_4#
        Original English: "There is something you could help me with, if you have time."
        Translation: "時間があるなら、頼みたいことがあるんだが。"
    },
    {
        &dia_5#
        Original English: "I could use your help one time."
        Translation: "一度きりでいい。手を貸してくれないか。"
    },
    {
        &dia_6#
        Original English: "Hey there friend, anything I can help you with?"
        Translation: "やあ、相棒。何か用かい？"
    },
    {
        &dia_7#
        Original English: "Now, anything I can help you with?"
        Translation: "さて、何か頼みたいことでも？"
    },
    {
        &dia_8#
        Original English: "I found this "first item", is it yours?"
        Translation: "これを見つけたんだが。"first item"だ。あんたのか？"
    },
    {
        &dia_9#
        Original English: "I found this "second item", is it yours?"
        Translation: "これを見つけたんだが。"second item"だ。あんたのか？"
    },
    {
        &dia_10#
        Original English: "What could I help you with?"
        Translation: "何の用だい？"
    },
    {
        &dia_11#
        Original English: "What was it that you wanted again?"
        Translation: "ええっと、何の用だったかな？"
    },
    {
        &dia_12#
        Original English: "Can you improve my items?"
        Translation: "装備を強化してくれないか？"
    },
    {
        &dia_13#
        Original English: "Nothing right now."
        Translation: "今は何もない。"
    },
    {
        &dia_14#
        Original English: "Yes! How did you know I was looking for it?"
        Translation: "そう、それだ！ どうして探してたのが分かったんだい？"
    },
    {
        &dia_15#
        Original English: "Yes! That's exactly it."
        Translation: "そう、まさにそれだ！"
    },
    {
        &dia_16#
        Original English: "Yes! But I can't use it yet. Without my "first item" it's useless. Keep it for now."
        Translation: "そう！ だが、まだ使えん。"first item"がなけりゃ、ただの飾りだ。今は持っておいてくれ。"
    },
    {
        &dia_17#
        Original English: "Greetings, how can I be of assistance?"
        Translation: "いらっしゃい、ご用件を伺おう。"
    },
    {
        &dia_18#
        Original English: "Reset my perks"
        Translation: "パークをリセットする"
    },
    {
        &dia_19#
        Original English: "Clear my inventory"
        Translation: "所持品を空にする"
    },
    {
        &dia_20#
        Original English: "Spawn some enemies"
        Translation: "敵を出現させる"
    },
    {
        &dia_21#
        Original English: "Nothing right now."
        Translation: "今は何もない。"
    },
    {
        &dia_22#
        Original English: "Yes! That's exactly what that thief stole!"
        Translation: "そう、それだ！ あの泥棒が盗んでいったのは、まさにそれ！"
    },
    {
        &dia_23#
        Original English: "I lost an item, it can be found somewhere under the water."
        Translation: "あるものを失くしてしまったんだ。たしか、水の下のどこかに沈んでいるはずなんだが。"
    },
    {
        &dia_24#
        Original English: "One of my items was stolen, thief should still be nearby."
        Translation: "持ち物のひとつを盗まれた。あの泥棒、まだ近くにいるはずだ。"
    },
    {
        &dia_25#
        Original English: "I am so gratefull!"
        Translation: "本当に助かったよ！"
    },
    {
        &dia_26#
        Original English: "I am so glad you cought him before he run away."
        Translation: "逃げられる前に捕まえてくれて、本当に良かった。"
    },
    {
        &dia_27#
        Original English: "Can you help me recover it?"
        Translation: "取り返すのを手伝ってくれないか？"
    },
    {
        &dia_28#
        Original English: "Can you get it of him?"
        Translation: "あいつから取り返してくれないか？"
    },
    {
        &dia_29#
        Original English: "I'll be there in a bit."
        Translation: "すぐに向かう。"
    },
    {
        &dia_30#
        Original English: "System"
        Translation: "システム"
    },
    {
        &dia_31#
        Original English: "Yes! I was just about to ask you to recover that!"
        Translation: "そう、それだ！ ちょうどそれを取り戻してほしいって頼もうとしていたところなんだ！"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_1#
        Original English: "Oh, you're not from around here. And you don't look plagued either."
        Translation: "おお……この辺りのモンじゃないな。それに、感染もしてないみたいだ。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_2#
        Original English: "I don't suppose you remember what floor this is? "
        Translation: "ここが何層目か、分かったりしないか？"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_3#
        Original English: "You don't talk much do you?"
        Translation: "……あんまり喋らないんだな。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_4#
        Original English: "A mute friend. Heh-heh."
        Translation: "無口な友達ってわけか。……はは。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_5#
        Original English: "Since we're friends now. I suggest you avoid the brute over there."
        Translation: "せっかく知り合ったんだ。向こうのバケモンには近づかない方がいい。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_6#
        Original English: "I would tell you about myself, but I'm afraid I don't remember much. "
        Translation: "自分のことを話したいのは山々なんだが……ほとんど思い出せない。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_7#
        Original English: "... part of a reconaissance patrol..."
        Translation: "偵察隊にいた。たぶん。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_8#
        Original English: "I don't remember much else, God-Emperor forgive me. "
        Translation: "他はもう思い出せない。神帝陛下、お許しを。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_9#
        Original English: "Sometimes I close my eyes and by the time I open them, I'm somewhere else entirely. "
        Translation: "時々、目を閉じて……次に開く頃には、まるで別の場所にいる。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_10#
        Original English: "How I'm still alive must be a miracle in itself. "
        Translation: "まだ生きてるのが奇跡みたいなもんだ。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_11#
        Original English: "Here, take this - it'll be of help along the way. I'm done for anyways."
        Translation: "ほら、これ持ってけ。道中の役にはなる。俺はもう長くない。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_12#
        Original English: "Good luck out there."
        Translation: "気をつけて行けよ。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_13#
        Original English: "I envy you, you're very brave."
        Translation: "正直、羨ましいよ。あんたは勇気がある。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_14#
        Original English: "How long have we been here?"
        Translation: "俺たち、どれくらいここにいるんだろうな。"
    },
    {
        &dia_abandonedSoldier_15#
        Original English: "Farewell."
        Translation: "じゃあな。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Yaroslav_1#
        Original English: "Welcome to the anomaly. The dream of uncertainty. Here, even reality amounts to nothing."
        Translation: "ようこそ、アノマリーへ。不確かさの見せる夢だ。ここでは、現実さえ何の意味も持たない。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Yaroslav_2#
        Original English: "Time is not of the essence here… Only choice. Soon, you’ll feel it yourself."
        Translation: "ここでは時間は本質ではない。ただ選択だけがある。やがて、君自身もそれを感じ取ることになる。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Yaroslav_3#
        Original English: "Sometimes, I hear it all again. The voice of a girl… The color of her eyes… Frightening yet beautiful… Like mornings at war. Hours before the storm… You breathe in deeply, for it may be your last. The vast sky… And between the cold air and the smoke, a ray of sunlight on your face…"
        Translation: "時折、あの全てがまた聞こえてくる。少女の声、その瞳の色、恐ろしくも、美しい。戦場の朝のようだ。嵐の数刻前、人は深く息を吸う。それが最期になるかもしれないから。広大な空、冷たい空気と煙の合間に、頬を撫でる一筋の陽光……。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Yaroslav_4#
        Original English: "Beyond those gates, you will have to carry the greatest burden of all - your own!"
        Translation: "あの門の向こうで、君は何より重い荷を背負うことになる――他ならぬ、君自身という荷を。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Yaroslav_5#
        Original English: "The crusade they’ve mustered is blind with power... my own kind, crippled by ignorance… we are lost… lost in the wilderness!"
        Translation: "奴らが結集した聖戦の軍勢は、力に目を眩ませている。同胞たちは無知によって萎え、立つこともままならない……。我々は迷っている……。荒野に、迷い続けている。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Yaroslav_6#
        Original English: "I have not seen her for so long, I wonder if she was even real… A daughter imagined in dreams perhaps… Winds be with her."
        Translation: "長らく会っていないせいで、本当に実在したのかさえ覚束ない……。夢の中で思い描いた娘だったのかもしれない……。どうか、風が彼女と共にあらんことを。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Yaroslav_7#
        Original English: "I too am tired, but I gaze into the fire as it burns slowly - my eyes wide open. Some moths gather around the flame and they fly straight into it. Others fly in too and even more follow… All night long, without as much as a rustle, they melt away... I did not fear death then… but I was beginning to fear for my life."
        Translation: "私もまた、疲れ果てている。だが、ゆっくりと燃える炎を、目を見開いて見つめる。蛾が炎の周りに集い、まっすぐに飛び込んでいく。続く者も、その後の者も……。一晩中、衣擦れの音ひとつ立てずに、溶けるように消えていく。あの頃、私は死を恐れてはいなかった。だが、生きることを恐れ始めていた。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Yaroslav_8#
        Original English: "We enslaved what was left of the Forsaken…  We crucified the Mechanomads for raiding time itself… We brought light to darkness and blinded all who refused to see.... And even here, at the gates to the anomaly, we flay all who dare approach. You understand such methods…. After all, your own path is a river of blood and deception…"
        Translation: "我々は、フォーセイクンの生き残りを奴隷とした。時そのものを荒らした罪で、メカノマドを磔にした。闇に光をもたらし、見ようとしない者たちの目を全て潰した。そして今、このアノマリーの門前ですら、近づこうとする者を皮剥にしている。君にも、こうしたやり方は分かるだろう。何しろ、君が歩んできた道もまた、血と欺瞞の川なのだから。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Yaroslav_9#
        Original English: "When you return, Collector, things will not be as they were. You will not be as you were."
        Translation: "戻ってきた時には、コレクター、何もかもがかつてのままではない。君自身もまた、かつての君ではないだろう。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Julia_1#
        Original English: "This crusade is not only about the city… Yaroslav is to be apprehended. As long as his example can inspire others, there can be no peace."
        Translation: "この遠征は、単に都市のためだけのものではありません。ヤロスラフは拘束しなければなりません。彼の存在が誰かを奮い立たせる限り、平穏は訪れませんから。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Julia_2#
        Original English: "I hope you don't judge what you see. We both know justice exists only between those equal in strength. For as it stands, the strong do what they wish, and the weak suffer what they must. "
        Translation: "どうか、目にしたものだけで判断しないでください。正義というものは、力の釣り合った者同士の間にしか成立しません。結局のところ、強者は望むままに振る舞い、弱者は与えられた苦痛を受け入れるしかないのです。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Julia_3#
        Original English: "I will confide in you a recent detail. There is a traitor within our higher ranks - I can tolerate many things... but betrayal..."
        Translation: "ひとつ、お話ししておきたいことがあります。上層部の中に裏切り者がいます。私は大抵のことには目をつぶれますが、裏切りだけは別です。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Julia_4#
        Original English: "I’ll speak frankly with you… This population is lost. The corruption spreads from the anomaly, and even our soldiers are affected… As for the citizens, they were strange to begin with… but many are now completely off the handle. So… I ask of you kindly… Do your part, and I‘ll see to it that we all return as victors. "
        Translation: "率直に申し上げます。この区域の住民は、もう手遅れです。腐敗はアノマリーから広がり、兵士たちにまで影響を及ぼしています。市民も元々どこか歪でしたが、今では多くが完全に均衡を失っています。ですから、あなたには役目を果たしていただきたいのです。そうすれば、私が必ず、皆を勝者として帰還させます。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Julia_5#
        Original English: "This crusade has gone on for too long, yet… it seems as if we have only arrived here. "
        Translation: "この遠征は、あまりにも長く続いています。それなのに、不思議と、私たちは今ようやく到着したばかりのようにも感じるのです。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Julia_6#
        Original English: "I miss the wind… The cold air, weaving its way around you as you take in the horizon. "
        Translation: "風が恋しいですね……。地平線を眺めている時、身体の周囲を静かに流れていく、あの冷たい空気が。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Julia_7#
        Original English: "To guide by authority, to graft tradition onto peace, to bestow mercy upon the conquered… to wage war until the proud kneel."
        Translation: "権威によって導き、平穏へ秩序を接ぎ、敗者には慈悲を与える。そして、傲慢な者たちが跪くまで戦い続ける。それが我々の役目です。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Julia_8#
        Original English: "I do not merely rely on you - I trust in you. Don’t let me down."
        Translation: "私は、あなたに頼っているだけではありません。信頼しています。失望させないでくださいね。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Julia_9#
        Original English: "The Serdar occupation of the gate is only a part of the problem. We also have to deal with the corruption from beyond…  "
        Translation: "セルダルによる門の占拠は、問題の一部に過ぎません。我々は、その先から流れ込んでくる腐敗そのものにも対処しなければならないのです。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Julia_10#
        Original English: "Farewell."
        Translation: "では、またお会いしましょう。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Abelard_1#
        Original English: "Gets lonely out here. Thank the God-Emperor for the voices that haunt me…"
        Translation: "こんな場所じゃ寂しくてかなわん。憑いてくる声共に……。神帝陛下に感謝を。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Abelard_2#
        Original English: "Who knows what Yaroslav is up to. To turn on his own… so brutally. Tsss!"
        Translation: "ヤロスラフが何を企んでるか知れたもんじゃない。仲間に牙を剥くとは……。それも、あんなに残酷に。チッ！"
    },
    {
        &dia_Abelard_3#
        Original English: "Serdar filth!"
        Translation: "セルダルの屑共め！"
    },
    {
        &dia_Abelard_4#
        Original English: "No order to this place. There’s no cycle, no ebb and flow to the city. It all feels like… Eh. What do you care anyway."
        Translation: "この街には秩序ってもんがない。循環も、満ち引きもない。何もかも……。ふん、あんたには関係ないか。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Abelard_5#
        Original English: "War is Hell. Not a sewer, so I don’t exactly know what you are doing here…"
        Translation: "戦は地獄だ。あんたみたいなのが来る場所じゃないと思うんだがな。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Abelard_6#
        Original English: "We all have our role to play. You play yours. We’ll see about mine!"
        Translation: "誰しも演じる役回りがある。あんたはあんたの役を演じるがいい。俺の役は、これから見もの、ってとこだな！"
    },
    {
        &dia_Abelard_7#
        Original English: "Farewell."
        Translation: "達者でな。"
    },
    {
        &dia_ArchInquisitor_1#
        Original English: "I empathize with those we purify… But when I lay my hands on the Serdars… Hell will seem like Heaven!"
        Translation: "浄化される者たちにも、私とて同情を抱く。だが、セルダルの輩がこの手にかかれば……。地獄の方が、天国に思えることだろう！"
    },
    {
        &dia_ArchInquisitor_2#
        Original English: "If we could only do away with everything here, altogether…"
        Translation: "ここのもの全て、根絶やしにできれば良いのだが。"
    },
    {
        &dia_ArchInquisitor_3#
        Original English: "A marvellous conception, a supreme figure, an exalted shadow, an infinite representation of the excellence and supremacy that transcends comprehension or grasp. Thus is the excellence of the God-Emperor and the greatness of his domains made manifest. He will be glorified not in one, but in countless suns. Not in a single realm but in a thousand!"
        Translation: "比類なき観念、至高なる御姿、崇高なる影、理解も把握も及ばぬ卓越と至上を映す、無限の表象。神帝陛下の卓越と、その御領の偉大さは、かくして顕れる。神帝陛下は、ただ一つの太陽にではなく、数え切れぬ太陽の中で讃えられるのだ。一つの世界にではなく、千の世界に！"
    },
    {
        &dia_ArchInquisitor_4#
        Original English: "I do not like forced conversations, so - if you please…"
        Translation: "強いられた会話は好まぬ。故に――。"
    },
    {
        &dia_ArchInquisitor_5#
        Original English: "There is no meaning to an existence with no beginning and no end, and I no longer wish to indulge it with conversation. Out of my sight."
        Translation: "始まりも終わりもない存在に、意味など無い。もはや会話で構ってやる気もない。視界から消えろ。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Anselm_1#
        Original English: "Another traitor."
        Translation: "また裏切者か。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Anselm_2#
        Original English: "Have you heard about the Serdars… Savages."
        Translation: "セルダルどもの話、聞いたか。野蛮な連中だ。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Anselm_3#
        Original English: "Sometimes I wonder how it really is in the Inquisition."
        Translation: "時々考えるんだ。審問団の内側ってのは、実際どうなってるのか。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Anselm_4#
        Original English: "The titles, the scrolls, incantations…"
        Translation: "称号だの、巻物だの、呪文だの。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Anselm_5#
        Original English: "One of the inquisitors has a soft spot for all the weird things happening here… The gentle one."
        Translation: "審問官の一人が、この街で起きてる奇妙なこと全部に、妙に肩入れしているらしい。あの、物腰の柔らかい奴だ。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Anselm_6#
        Original English: "I think a lot about why we are here… But it’s not going well since I’m not much of a thinker."
        Translation: "我々がなぜここにいるのか、よく考えるんだ……。だが、俺は大して頭の回る方じゃないから、考えはちっともまとまらん。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Anselm_7#
        Original English: "There’s something in the air."
        Translation: "何か、空気の中に感じるんだ。"
    },
    {
        &dia_stranger_1#
        Original English: "That's quite the leap you made down there."
        Translation: "いやはや、なかなかの跳躍だったな。"
    },
    {
        &dia_stranger_2#
        Original English: "I hope you weren't expecting to find, something special up here."
        Translation: "ここで何か特別なものでも見つかると、期待していなければいいのだが。"
    },
    {
        &dia_stranger_3#
        Original English: "Why don't you have a seat? You look tired... it's quiet here."
        Translation: "座っていかないか。疲れているようだね。ここは静かだ。"
    },
    {
        &dia_stranger_4#
        Original English: "You may find yourself reminiscing the quiet moments..."
        Translation: "いずれ君も、こうした静かな時間を懐かしむようになるかもしれない。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_1#
        Original English: "Hmmm - a visitor."
        Translation: "ふむ……来客ですか。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_2#
        Original English: "A visitor to a plague at that - a rare occurence. Ah! The Administration? Yes - that much is now obvious."
        Translation: "それも、この疫禍の只中へ訪れるとは珍しい。ああ、統治機構の関係者ですか？なるほど。そのくらいは分かります。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_3#
        Original English: "Always a pervasive need for the world to make sense - but with each passing moment, I find the omnistructure is always one step beyond it… beyond comprehension."
        Translation: "人は何にでも意味を求めたがります。ですが、時が経つほどに思うのです。オムニストラクチャは、その理解の一歩先にあり続けるのだと。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_4#
        Original English: "I wonder what tales you’d share if only you could speak. Traversing every crevice and ruin on foot, my, my… the secrets you hold... and what happens to the ones you leave behind? Do you ever think of them?"
        Translation: "あなたが話せたなら、どんな話を聞かせてくれるのでしょうね。あらゆる裂け目や廃墟を、自らの足で渡り歩いてきたのでしょう。あなたの知ること。あなたが抱えている秘密。そして、後に残してきた人々のこと。……時々、思い出したりしますか？"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_5#
        Original English: "It sounds like a treacherous life... You must not know much kindness. And how could you - I imagine you've experienced pain and death uncountable times. It is after all reflected in your demeanour."
        Translation: "危険な生き方です。あなたはあまり優しさに恵まれてこなかったのでしょうね。ですが、それも無理はありません。苦痛や死と、数え切れないほど向き合ってきたのでしょうから。不思議なものです。そういうことは、案外表情よりも佇まいに現れる。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_6#
        Original English: "Maybe this can make a small change."
        Translation: "これが、少しでも助けになればよいのですが。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_7#
        Original English: "You know, I myself am not a stranger to challenges .This struggle between absolute power and perfect order is no longer easy to balance. I find myself giving it my all, without, seeing much in return..."
        Translation: "実のところ、私も苦労とは無縁ではありません。絶対的な力と完全な秩序。その二つの間で均衡を保つことは、年々難しくなっています。力を尽くしてはいますが、その成果が見えることは稀ですね。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_8#
        Original English: "The Serdars now complicate things... Their sacrifices were too great for a wavering Empire. Yet rebelling against everything makes life lose its purpose..."
        Translation: "セルダルの存在が事態をさらに難しくしています。帝国にとって、彼らの犠牲はあまりにも大きかった。ですが、あらゆるものに反抗し続ければ、人はやがて目的そのものを失います。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_9#
        Original English: "The Administration’s vision of order is sterile however... perfect, yes, but like marble - its beauty frozen permanently in the rhythm of death. In his few moments of peace, Yaroslav would probably explain it better than I - then again - his word was always as sharp as his saber."
        Translation: "もっとも、統治機構の秩序にも問題はあります。完璧ではありますが、生気がない。大理石の彫像のようなものです。美しい。ですが、その美しさは死の中で固定されている。ヤロスラフなら、私より上手く説明したでしょうね。もっとも――彼の言葉は、いつもサーベルのように鋭かった。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_10#
        Original English: "We both have work to do. Until we meet again."
        Translation: "お互い、まだ仕事が残っています。またお会いしましょう。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_11#
        Original English: "Ah, a familiar visitor. I suppose you journey into the core, but you've come to visit first? "
        Translation: "おや。また来てくださったのですね。そろそろ中核へ向かわれる頃かと思っていましたが、その前に立ち寄ってくださったのでしょうか。"
    },
    {
        &dia_Alexius_12#
        Original English: "Well that is a kindness returned. You are ever more nuanced than I thought. I bid you farewell then, this is where we part ways - for now. "
        Translation: "それは嬉しい心遣いです。あなたは私が思っていたより、ずっと複雑な方らしい。では、お別れです。ここで道は分かれます。……今はまだ、ですが。"
    },
    {
        &dia_MysteriousWoman_1#
        Original English: "I know what you are… But - how can there be anything interesting about a being that never transforms? Hm hm hm…  "
        Translation: "あんたが何者かは分かってるよ。でも――決して変容しない存在に、何の面白みがあるって言うんだろうね？ ふふふ……。"
    },
    {
        &dia_MysteriousWoman_2#
        Original English: "So… What do you think of the city? Quite a few nutcases eh?"
        Translation: "で……この街、どう思う？ 頭のいかれた連中ばかりでしょ？"
    },
    {
        &dia_MysteriousWoman_3#
        Original English: "Stealing always has deep roots among the poor. The children steal, and fathers and mothers too! Back when I was on duty in the rough quarters, I would often be robbed of whatever I happened to be carrying."
        Translation: "盗みっていうのは、貧しい者たちの間に深く根付いてるのよ。子供も盗む、父親も母親も盗む！ あたしが下町で勤めてた頃なんて、持ち歩いてたものは何でも、しょっちゅう奪われてたわ。"
    },
    {
        &dia_MysteriousWoman_4#
        Original English: "My cloak, my gloves, even my tools…  what do they even do with such things? I was performing a surgery on one of the afflicted once, with his family standing there. "
        Translation: "外套、手袋、果ては道具まで。あんなもの、持ち去って何の役に立つって言うのかしら？ 一度なんかは、罹患者の手術をしている最中だったのよ。家族がすぐ脇に立っていてね。"
    },
    {
        &dia_MysteriousWoman_5#
        Original English: "I’m about to give him a sip of the asylum brew to ease the pain, and when I turn back - it’s gone! The little ones, smiling at me with their tiny teeth… He he he…"
        Translation: "痛みを和らげるために、収容所の煎じ薬をひと口飲ませようとして――振り返ったら、もう消えてるじゃないの！ 小さな子供たちが、ちっちゃな歯を見せて、にこにこ笑ってるのよ……ふふふ……。"
    },
    {
        &dia_MysteriousWoman_6#
        Original English: "Agh… Probably addicted to it… Kleptomania. Another condition that needs curing… "
        Translation: "あぁ……たぶん中毒なんでしょうね……盗癖ってやつよ。これもまた、治癒が必要な病だわ……。"
    },
    {
        &dia_MysteriousWoman_7#
        Original English: "There’s a merchant around here that’s bound to have some of that brew, I’m sure. Perhaps you should seek him out! Or if you find a bottle or two - well, I’m not going anywhere!"
        Translation: "この辺りに、その薬を扱ってる商人が必ずいるはずよ。あんた、探してみるといいわ！ あるいはもし、瓶のひとつふたつ見つけてきてくれたら――まあ、あたしはどこにも行かないからね！"
    },
    {
        &dia_MysteriousWoman_8#
        Original English: "Say - that vessel of yours? Now that’s something I’d tinker with… How much would you sell it for? "
        Translation: "ねえ――あんたのその器、あれね、いじり回してみたいものだわ……。いくらで売ってくれる？"
    },
    {
        &dia_MysteriousWoman_9#
        Original English: "They say there’s no genius without a touch of madness… What about those where madness is in abundance? Ha ha ha!"
        Translation: "天才には狂気がつきもの、なんて言うけれど……。狂気が有り余ってる連中はどうなるのかしらね？ あはははは！"
    },
    {
        &dia_MysteriousWoman_10#
        Original English: "Ahhh…. *hums happily*"
        Translation: "ああ……。"
    }
]